let's uh try and understand the puzzle
that z is turning out to be and the
recent developments over there let me
welcome on board then abnesh roy to talk
about exactly that abnesh hi good to
have you in the show what is it that
you're making of these developments with
z
i think uh this was uh expected uh with
just uh 3.99
sake of promoters in my view this was
just a case of when rather than if
specially given the stock was
languishing for a lot of time in spite
of mid caps and a lot of the other
consumer names media and stocks doing
well
uh key thing to watch here will be
today's india and we also need the
clarity whether the idiom will also be
needed for full clarity
uh this is exactly similar uh to what
was seen in dish tv few days back so
there also yes bank the largest
shareholder or dish tv had asked for
removal of the managing director and the
other independent directors post that if
you see in the last few days this tv
stock has moved up almost 25 30 percent
uh so clearly uh these stocks are
available at a very comfortable and in
fact cheap valuation
and there has been essentially concern
at the promoter level uh we did the uh
the company addressing lot of the
promoter concerns in the last one year
which was a good development and the
stock had related also partly had gone
to 250 to 60. so the stock the company
had addressed lot of the concerns so
they were giving out
a quarterly key balance sheet numbers
they were sharing the related party
transactions with this tv city cable
they were giving more clarity on the
investments they were giving out numbers
for
so they were giving out a lot of these
numbers they had also defocused on sugar
box which was clearly seen as a uh
diversification from the core business
and uh
you now need to see four things uh one
is of course uh
who who is the new leadership if
the what investor has asked those things
get approved uh what is the new uh
leadership
are all the board members which are
proposed by investor you need to see
that the constitution of the board you
need to see that also uh in terms of uh
the current uh team below
you would need to see uh uh on on the
continuity of that currency the
flagship channel is going through a
revamp they are launching a lot of new
content a new marketing campaign so we
would need to see uh
and address that also on a fundamental
aspect z is improving market share
quarter on quarter our sense is around
100 improvement is likely in q2 from the
q1 disappointment so whenever pandemic
happens
z loses market share because they don't
have uh
much of content in the
in the comedy space and the crime filler
space where some of their competitors
have an edge so now we would expect a z
as a network to get back around 100
market share and because economy is also
opening up overall advertising is
looking up and we do have season coming
up lot of the sectors in the pandemic
did not have a proper business uh case
to advertise and those sectors will come
back fmcg continuing to do well other
parts of the consumer are also doing
well
so fundamentally z is a very cheap stock
at 10 12 times b multiple forward uh
with the dividend paying company net
debt zero uh and uh it's in the broader
consumption space so i will say that if
all these things go right we have a new
board and more independences
now what is
the guarantee that
the new board
or the new management will be able to do
a better job than what the current board
is not doing
these
usp has been their ability to generate
content at a significantly lower price
than what others are doing
the current promoters or founders or the
management in this case they have
mastered the art of creating content and
they understand the indian landscape
like never before
change of god
i mean there is no guarantee that will
be good news
i would partly agree with what you are
saying c is seen as a low cost and more
focused on sustainable content rather
than some other competitors who use the
big dollar kind of a content which is
not sustainable z being a listed company
did have that constraint and that's why
if you see star has got around 24
network share uh non-sports and v has
got around 18 to 19 sustained uh market
share in q1 they went flow because of
the pandering you are partly right but
uh unlike a bank business for example if
banks there are issues in terms of
corporate governance etc the deposits go
away
media is a brand and that's why the
library is there the brand is there and
the
the current uh management or the teacher
management knows what is the usb of g it
is not rocket science they also know
that
sony has got a particular style star has
got a particular style if i copy that i
think it will be me too so i will say i
don't think that's a big risk uh yes
punisher has done a decent job
from a fundamental aspect he has focused
on the business he exited sport he has
gone into new regional uh businesses
most of which are doing well yes there
has been a lot loss in market share in
the flagship channel but in such a large
bouquet of channels there is always
going to be some wins and some losses
but i will say what you have highlighted
is a small risk i don't see that as a
decrease when you have such a big
network and when you have a brand and
such a large library plus they have
already done the hard work in d5 i don't
think that's a very big risk and the new
management also or the existing
management also is doing a detailed job
the more concern was essentially
the the uh
the conference which came
coming in terms of either
the puppet governance which came in the
last two years then we had the
investor relation that uh insider
trading all those those were the biggest
concerns so i think fundamentally the
company is still doing reasonably well
given the constraints of a district
entity but yes what you highlighted i
think the management will continue to
maintain the usp of that channel rather
than becoming a metoo
then it will not work